<?xml version="1.0"?>
<PluginConfig>
	<Version>1.0</Version>
	
	<Access>
		<Default>voice</Default>
		<pick>op</pick>
	</Access>
	
	<Help>
		<Brief>
CALC - Perform simple math calculations.
CONVERT - Convert values between many known units (i.e. temp, weight, volume).
RAND - Generate a random number given a maximum or range.
ROLL - Roll dice for use in Roll Playing Games, such as Dungeons &amp; Dragons.
HASH - Generate MD5 hash of string, or a random source.
PICK - Pick a random user from the channel, and notify them.
8BALL - Ask the magic 8-ball a question.
		</Brief>
		<Detail>
			<calc>
CALC expression
This command performs simple math calculations, and posts the answer to the channel (or user if in a private message).  Examples:
-
!calc 45 + 5
!calc (374634 * 34) / 500.1
!calc 2 ** 8
			</calc>
			<convert>
CONVERT value units to units
-
This command converts numerical values between various units, such as temperature, weight and volume.  It posts the answer to the channel (or user if in a private message).  For example, you could type "!convert 45 lbs to kg" to convert pounds to kilograms, which would output 20.41165665 kg.  Examples:
-
!convert 100 lbs to kg
!convert 25 C to F
!convert 5 mm to in
!convert 1 gallon to cm^3
!convert 4500 rpm to hz
			</convert>
			<rand>
RAND
RAND max
RAND min - max
-
This command picks a random number, and emits the result.  Without any parameters, it picks a floating point decimal between 0.0 and 1.0.  With one number specified, it is treated as the maximum, and picks a number between 0 and it.  With two numbers specified, they are treated as a range.  Will round down to nearest integer if only integers are provided, otherwise it will use floats.  Uses an ultra-random number generator.
			</rand>
			<roll>
ROLL dice
ROLL dice +/- modifier
-
This command rolls dice for use in RPGs like Dungeons &amp; Dragons.  It can roll any number of any-sided die, plus or minus a modifier.  The syntax for the dice is (NUM)d(SIDES), and the optional modifier is simply +/-(NUMBER).  Uses an ultra-random number generator.  Examples:
-
!roll 1d6
!roll 2d20
!roll 1d100 +20
			</roll>
			<hash>
HASH
HASH string
-
This command computes an MD5 digest (hash) given a source string, or creates a random one if nothing is provided.  The output is 32-characters in length, lower-case, and hexadecimal encoded.
			</hash>
			<pick>
PICK
-
This command picks a random user from the current channel.  All nicks that end in "bot" or "serv" are excluded, as well as the bot itself (even if its name doesn't end in "bot").  The idea is to pick humans only.  The chosen user's nickname is emitted to the channel.  Uses an ultra-random number generator.
			</pick>
		</Detail>
	</Help>
</PluginConfig>
