<?xml version="1.0"?>
<PluginConfig>
	<Version>1.0</Version>
	
	<!-- API Key for free.worldweatheronline.com -->
	<APIKey></APIKey>
	
	<DegreeUnits>C (F)</DegreeUnits>
	<WindSpeedUnits>K (M)</WindSpeedUnits>
	
	<Access>
		<Default>voice</Default>
	</Access>
	
	<Help>
		<Brief>
WEATHER - Get current conditions for US zip code or 'city country'.
FORECAST - Set 5 day forecast for US zip code or 'city country'.
LOCATION - Set your default location and time zone for future queries.
		</Brief>
		<Detail>
			<weather>
WEATHER location
-
Get current weather conditions.  Specify any 5-digit US ZIP code (uses Yahoo! Weather), or any city and country separated by spaces (uses WorldWeatherOnline.com).  For example, 'weather guelph canada' or 'weather toronto ca'.  Countries can be abbreviated.
-
To get weather for countries outside the US, you will need to register for a free API Key at: http://developer.worldweatheronline.com/
After signing up, copy your API key and paste it into this command:
-
!config set Weather/APIKey YOUR_API_KEY_HERE
-
At this point the Weather Plugin should be ready to use.  Test it out by checking your local weather: "!weather london england".
			</weather>
			<forecast>
FORECAST location
-
Get a 5-day forecast for the specified location, which can be any 5-digit US ZIP code, or any city and country separated by spaces.  For example, 'forecast guelph canada' or 'forecast toronto ca'.  Countries can be abbreviated.
See "!help weather" for details on setting up your API key for WorldWeatherOnline.com (it's free).
			</forecast>
			<location>
LOCATION city state country
LOCATION zipcode
-
Set your location for future weather and date/time queries, which the bot remembers.  This also looks up your time zone based on your location, and stores that for displaying and calculating dates and times for you.
See "!help weather" for details on setting up your API key for WorldWeatherOnline.com (used for the location service -- it's free).
			</location>
		</Detail>
	</Help>
</PluginConfig>
