<?xml version="1.0"?>
<PluginConfig>
	<Version>1.0</Version>
	
	<!-- API Key for dictionaryapi.com -->
	<DictAPIKey></DictAPIKey>
	
	<Access>
		<Default>voice</Default>
	</Access>
	
	<Help>
		<Brief>
GOOGLE - Perform Google search and return first result.
IMAGE - Perform Google image search and return direct URL to first result.
DEFINE - Define term using the Wikipedia API or DictionaryAPI.com.
SPELL - Spell check a word (uses DictionaryAPI.com).
URBAN - Define term using the Urban Dictionary API.
STOCK - Grab stock quote given company symbol (uses Yahoo Finance API).
		</Brief>
		<Detail>
			<google>
GOOGLE search-query
GOOGLE nickname
This uses the Google Search API to search for a query, and returns the first result.  If a username is specified, the last thing the user said is used as the query.  The result is emitted to the current channel.
			</google>
			<image>
IMAGE search-query
IMAGE nickname
This uses the Google Image Search API to search for an image given a text string, and returns a direct URL to the first result.  If a username is specified, the last thing the user said is used as the query.  The result is emitted to the current channel.  If you repeat the same query multiple times, it will cycle through the first 4 results.
			</image>
			<define>
DEFINE term
This uses the Wikipedia API to locate a suitable definition for a term.  The result is emitted to the current channel.  If a definition cannot be found, the bot also tries DictionaryAPI.com (Merriam-Webster), which requires a free API key.  Sign up at http://www.dictionaryapi.com/ and then configure your API key with this command:
-
!config set WebSearch/DictAPIKey YOUR_API_KEY_HERE
-
Note that this is optional, and the DEFINE command works just fine with Wikipedia for most terms.  The DictionaryAPI.com is mainly used as a fallback, if the Wikipedia API fails or it doesn't define a particular term.
			</define>
			<spell>
SPELL word
This command uses the free API provided by DictionaryAPI.com (Merriam-Webster) to check the spelling of a word.  If the word cannot be found in the dictionary, spelling suggestions are provided.  Please note that this API requires a free API key.  Sign up at http://www.dictionaryapi.com/ and then configure your API key with this command: 
-
!config set WebSearch/DictAPIKey YOUR_API_KEY_HERE
			</spell>
			<urban>
URBAN term
This uses the Urban Dictionary API to locate a suitable definition for a term.  The result is emitted to the current channel.  Beware: Urban Dictionary can be very NSFW.  Use this at your own risk.  Remember, you can restrict access for any command to be owner only: !access set urban owner
			</urban>
			<stock>
STOCK symbol
This uses the Yahoo Finance API to grab a stock quote for the given symbol.  It reports the current price and change.  Example: !stock GOOG
			</stock>
		</Detail>
	</Help>
</PluginConfig>
